Tell
Ajay
that if you are going to buy CO in the market, then
what doubt do you have in it, normal,
which course is trading in it or is it
indicative of this card or not, or
whether it supports that problem or
not, so to
understand the MD processor's chief guest present, first of all we have to know
what Shubh is, that there is a special staff
member, like he definitely loves, he
also does cash, so he is like a friend,
just by being there, there is a part which is involved in your process,
but why does the police need his personal memory,
if the police did
not have any problem, then he would go to
Byrne to get the data, which slows it down a lot, for example, if
you have to give money to the shopkeeper, then
you will take it
out quickly and give it, it will not take time,
if that money is in your bag and it will take a
lot of time to take it out, so
you were in the mood at the shop, when you have to take it out
of your pocket, on this day you have to take it out
from the send bank, so to
make it faster, the cash account has been mentioned,
cadets of profits for processor, now the
RAM in the system  We call it
D length and dynamic Ram and Sita's Ram is
called SM and static Ram, it is
a little expensive but it is more
for student d.m.  So the processor
uses leveled cache.
How does this happen? The
processor searches for the data it needs on the L1.
If it doesn't find it there, it goes to the L2.
If that data isn't available on the
L3, it
goes to the L3. Airtel also has a lot of recent
sales. If it does
n't find that data, the processor goes to the L1 processor,
which is installed in our systems,
like 1GB, 16GB, and so on. In all three
worlds, the biggest losers are slower,
but the L1 processors are smaller and faster. So,
while buying a processor, the biggest thing is to say that the L1 processor is more
expensive and increases, and
if you are going for more cores and more threads, then
definitely
more data will come with it. Now you must have understood this logic,
but
what is the logic of this common TV and how does it work?
Basically, phase chips
are designed to be placed side by side. The
chip in the middle of it also uses leveled cache technology. The
MD has entered into this.  A cache
cost has been added to the 3D Cacheless
so that signals
can travel faster over distances, or we can also say that to
increase optical performance,
they have installed health chest players on the Jubilee CD search,
which is known as 3D TV
technology. If
we go into this in a little more detail, we can see what kind of
technology 3D is.
To increase the testosterone between teams, three
tablets have been placed one above the other on the entry cache.
One of these tablets is 32MB.
Similarly, three 32MB tablets have been
placed one above the other, which increases the
total testosterone of NCC cadets by 6MB.
Now, the L3 Cache is slower than the
Alfabe and Alto, but
faster than the Friend. So, obviously, the
L3 Cache is three times faster.
In simple words, the JCO can handle
games and multi-instructions of high-end software
very easily. This told us all that
SPSS matters the most in games,
so the data required by the CPU is stored
in the cache.  He searches for it and if he does
n't find it there, he goes to Ram who
reduces the number of favorites, but if the cashless is
more and he gets the data he needs in it, then there will be
no need to go to Ram, he will take the patient data
and will not let the decision go down, this
process of World Cup fast
is called intensive training, now you must have understood the technology of NDTV, then you
can also enjoy mp3d cash, which comes
only with a license with Zee TV, if we talk about
its space, then in this you get
2016 friends, 4.5 complaint post
production points and its paste clock is the giver,
now the most special one is that
add ad is
of 512mb, to cash show is of MB and and
regression edition of Vikram Usendi, this
famous private job is available on that
too in your budget, you will
find the link in the description, so guys, that's all in this video, if you
liked the video then hit the like button and few
days and victories subscribe, I will
meet you in the next video